why are you here
你怎么在这儿
have they gone
走了吗
Why are they both here?
他们俩怎么也来了
Don't worry about them
不用管他们
Focus on the target first
先盯上目标
Isn't she your good friend?
她不是你好朋友吗
why are you following her
你为什么要跟踪她
You haven't answered my question yet
你还没回答我的问题呢
I will go to your company to find you
我 我去你们公司找你
Saw you following her
看见你跟着她
I followed here
我就跟过来了
What do you want from me?
找我干什么
I'd like to see you
我想看看你
How are you
最近过得怎么样
I'm fine
我挺好的
Then why are you following her?
那你为什么跟踪她
This is our company
这是我们公司
Task assigned by the boss
老板派的任务
What kind of mission is this?
这算什么任务啊
This is our company
这是我们公司
internal matters
内部的事情
Your boss asked you to check
是你们老板让你查的
It was someone from Yewu who asked you to check it.
还是夜雾的人让你查的
we have broken up
我们已经分手了
All my things from now on
以后我所有的事情
It has nothing to do with you
都跟你没有任何关系
Hello
喂
how is everything
怎么样啊
Detective Xiao Yao
名侦探小姚
Sorry Mr. Zhou
对不起 周总
I didn't keep up
我没跟上
It doesn't matter
没关系
Find a place to wait for me
找个地方等我
I'll come and pick you up
我过来接你
good
好
let's have dinner tonight
晚上一起吃饭
It was really Zhou Zheyi who asked you to check it.
真是周哲一让你查的
never again
以后不要再
Getting involved in my affairs
掺和我的事情了
May I
可以吗
The address she wrote when she joined the company
她入职写的地址
Not here
不是这儿
She deliberately concealed it
她故意隐瞒了
own address
自己的地址
Do you want to follow up and have a look?
要不要跟进去看看
Need not
不用
I don't know what's going on inside.
也不知道里面什么情况
Don't alarm her yet
先别惊动她了
Let's go
走吧
I can only say
我只能说
your choice and most
你的选择和大多数
People who work in information technology are different
做信息技术的人不一样
different options
不同的选择
is a different attitude and understanding
是不同的态度和理解
results
带来的结果
Mr. Zhou
周总
Today's things
今天的事情
I didn't do it well
是我没有办好
get off work
下班了
Not to mention work
不说工作了
enjoy it
好好享受
gourmet food
美食
If this matter
如果这件事情
Shiqi really did it
真是诗琪做的
you plan to
您打算
what to do with her
怎么处理她
What about me?
我这人呢
I definitely don’t want to be blackmailed
肯定是不想被勒索
but
但是呢
I don't want this to get serious either.
我也不希望这事搞大
If she is found
如果查到她
What about the specific address?
具体住址的话呢
I'll talk to her
我会找她聊一聊
If she agrees to negotiate a settlement
她同意协商解决的话
I know the past things
过往的事我会
Let bygones be bygones
既往不咎的
Thank you Mr. Zhou
谢谢周总
Can give her a chance
能给她一次机会
I'll bring you here
我带你来呢
I just want you to be happy
就是想你开心点
Let me tell you
我跟你说啊
Every time I was unhappy before
以前我每次不开心
I will call some good friends
我就会叫几个好朋友
Come over and eat together
一块儿过来吃东西
real
真的
Hot and spicy
热乎乎的 辣辣的
I was sweating after eating
吃完了之后一身汗
Really happy
特别开心 真的
I thought it looked like you
我还以为像您
Such successful people
这种成功人士
I don’t know how to eat from roadside stalls
不会吃路边摊呢
Isn't this outright prejudice?
这不是赤裸裸的偏见吗
In fact, I come less often now.
其实我现在来得少呢
Not because of anything else
不是因为别的
It's because before
是因为以前
Where are those buddies?
那些哥们儿呢
get married get married
结婚的结婚
Those who have children have children
有孩子的有孩子
It's not appropriate for me to call people out now.
我现在叫人出来不合适
I can't eat alone
我不能一个人来吃
right
是吧
You eat it
你吃啊
I think Mr. Zhou
我觉得 周总
people like you
像您这种人
Will never be out of date
永远都不会落伍的
because you think
因为你思想
I've always been very ahead of my time.
一直很超前啊
for example
比如
when you were in college
您上大学的时候
Already have something to ask for
就已经有了要
Founder of Q&A website
创办问答网站的
that kind of thought
那种念头
and persist until now
并且一直坚持到现在
Make it so big
做这么大
But it will definitely face
但是其中肯定面临
many important decisions
很多重要的决定
You made the right choice
您都做了对的选择
Very powerful
很厉害
my past history
对我过往的历史
I understand very clearly
了解得很清楚嘛
I'm not following you
我不是跟着您
Did you go to Thailand for an interview?
去泰国做了一次访谈吗
Also talk to the media
还跟媒体
Adapted some outlines and so on
对接了一些提纲什么的
That’s pretty much all I understand.
也就都了解差不多了
That's because I'm overthinking
那是我想多了
I thought you
我还以为你
Did you do some research on me?
考古了一下我呢
but
不过
There are many things in this
这里面有很多事情
I'm quite curious
我还挺好奇的
What's up
什么事
This website was originally
当初这个网站
When I can’t do it anymore
要做不下去的时候
I remember almost
我记得差不多
Two years, maybe
有两年时间吧
You haven't found financing yet
您都没有找到融资
Then how did you bring Zheyue with you?
那您是怎么带着哲阅
Keep at it
继续坚持下去的呀
I'm sorry
不好意思啊
Are employees
员工是不是
You shouldn't ask these questions
不应该问这些问题啊
You said you're off work now?
你说现在下班了啊
the two of us
咱们两个
Sit here and eat food stalls
坐在这儿吃大排档
Where else is there?
哪还有什么
There are differences between superiors and subordinates
上下级之分啊
Didn't answer you?
没回答你呢
How do I want to answer
我是想怎么回答
I was young then
那时候我年轻
There are so many ideas
想法也特别多
I do whatever comes to my mind
想到什么我就做什么
Tell the truth Zheyue
说实话哲阅
I did not do that
不是我做的
only one project
唯一一个项目
You have also developed other projects
你还开发过其他的项目
right
对
It's just that Zheyue is lucky
只是哲阅比较幸运
is the only one who survived
是唯一一个存活下来的
What about other projects?
那其他项目呢
died
死掉了
Or halfway
要不就是中途
I sold it
我给卖掉了
Then I use the money from selling it
然后我用卖掉的钱呢
go
去
Maintain the operation of the entire Zheyue?
维系整个哲阅的运营嘛
What other projects
那其他项目
Also like Zheyue
也像哲阅这样都是
Q&A website
问答网站
no no
不是 不是
There are other different projects
还有其他不同的项目
I don’t just make websites
我不光做网站
I still play games
我还做游戏呢
Have you also made games?
您还做过游戏呢
so amazing
太厉害了
What game? Can you tell me?
什么游戏呀 您说说看
Maybe I've played it
说不定我玩过
impossible
不可能
I made a prototype at that time
当时就做了一个雏形
Made a test version
弄了一个测试版
Not officially launched yet
都没有正式上线
What is that creativity?
那创意是什么呀
you say it
你说出来
Let me give you advice
让我参谋参谋嘛
What if it works?
那万一能成呢
Too cliche
太老套了
I definitely won't say it
我肯定不说的
Say what I am in your heart
说出来我在你心里的
Wouldn’t the glorious image be gone?
光辉形象不就没了吗
OK
行
If you don’t say it, don’t say it.
不说就不说
Zhou Shiqi is
周诗琪就是
The player in the game
游戏里的那个玩家
crow
乌鸦
At first I was just skeptical
一开始我只是怀疑
But Zhou Zheyi
但是周哲一
Let Yao Yao also investigate her
让姚瑶也调查她
I think it's possible
我觉得可能性
It's very big
就非常大了
Even if Shiqi is not a crow
即便诗琪不是乌鸦
But she must have something to do with Crow
但她跟乌鸦一定有关系
So what is Zhou Zheyi’s identity?
那周哲一什么身份
I doubt Zhou Zheyi
我怀疑周哲一
Just from Zhou Shiqi's hands
就是从周诗琪手里面
People who buy evidence
买证据的人
He is Mr. Z
他就是Z先生
Probably
很有可能
What does Zhou Shiqi have in her hands?
周诗琪手里到底掌握着
What's the secret of Zhe Yue?
哲阅什么秘密
Be sure to find out as soon as possible
一定要尽快地查清楚
As long as the thing is in her hands
东西只要在她手里
She will be in danger
她就会有危险
so i suggest
所以我建议
Inquire with her as soon as possible
尽早对她进行问询
Let her cooperate with our work
让她来配合我们的工作
But she is not a suspect
但是她不是犯罪嫌疑人
When asking
问询的时候
Be sure to pay attention to the methods
一定要注意方式方法
abide by rules and regulations
遵守规章制度
clear
明白
But this matter is still needed
但这件事情还是需要
carried out in secret
秘密地进行
I doubt this boss Zhang
我怀疑这个张老板
Already involved in it
已经参与在里边了
Boss Zhang
张老板
So fast
这么快
hard to use
不好用
Neither does Mr. Yu.
余先生也不会
Put it at your place
放在你那儿
But smart people
不过聪明的人
Often not so obedient
往往没那么听话
Do not worry
放心吧
I will deal with it
我会处理干净
Just these three sentences
就这三句
From the perspective of ambient sound
从环境音来看
I infer that this boss Zhang
我推断这个张老板
It should be the same as in the game
是应该跟游戏里边
someone is meeting
某个人在见面
second sentence
第二句
hard to use
不好用
Neither does Mr. Yu.
余先生也不会
Arrange it at your place
安排在你那儿
If this person is Yao Yao
如果这个人是姚瑶的话
That’s Zhou Zheyi
就是周哲一
If this inference is true
如果这个推断成立的话
So the first sentence
那么第一句
So fast
这么快
It should be referring to Yao Yao
指的应该就是姚瑶
recent tasks
最近的任务
Found Zhou Shiqi
查到的周诗琪
Recording time point
录音的时间节点
Discovered with Yao Yao
跟姚瑶发现
Zhou Shiqi’s time is consistent
周诗琪的时间是吻合的
The last sentence
最后一句
do not worry
你放心
I will deal with it
我会处理干净
This is obviously Zhou Zheyi
这显然是周哲一
I’m asking Boss Zhang for a favor.
在拜托张老板一件事
let her handle it
让她来处理
Things about Zhou Shiqi
周诗琪的事
possible
有可能
If Tianyang makes this judgment
如果天阳这个判断
is correct
是正确的
Must be as soon as possible
一定尽快
Get in touch with Zhou Shiqi
和周诗琪取得联系
Be sure to do it in secret
务必要秘密进行
clear
明白
Tianyang continues to stare at
天阳这面继续盯着
Boss Zhang’s movements
张老板动向
So clear
好 明白
Go back and have a good rest
回去好好休息啊
Be careful on the road, Mr. Zhou
路上小心啊 周总
Yao Yao
姚瑶
It seems like you guys get along pretty well.
看来你们相处得还不错
you follow me
你跟踪我
How can I be so boring?
我哪有那么无聊
I watched Zhou Zheyi
我看了周哲一
all interviews
所有的采访
I think he is
觉得他这个人
Very problematic
非常有问题
What does this have to do with me?
这跟我有什么关系啊
He has other plans for you
他对你另有企图
I'll go up and talk
我上去说吧
I promise to leave as soon as I finish speaking.
我保证说完就走
Say it
说吧
Your history with Zhou Zheyi
你对周哲一的历史
You should have some understanding
应该有些了解吧
It doesn’t matter if you don’t understand
不了解也没关系
Let me introduce you
我来给你介绍
In his early days in the United States
他早期在美国
When starting a Q&A website
创办问答网站的时候
I almost can't do it anymore
差点干不下去了
But suddenly
可突然间呢
A large amount of financing came
来了一大笔融资
bring him back to life
让他起死回生
Why does capital take a fancy to him?
资本为什么会看上他呢
I watched many interviews with him
我看了他很多采访
He has this history
他对这段历史
The description has always been very vague
一直描述得非常模糊
According to my survey
根据我的调查
At that time
那会儿
A small Q&A website like this
像他这种小型问答网站
It’s not just Zhou Zhe’s team
可不止周哲一一个团队
But why can he get up?
可他为什么能起来呢
Can you tell me the key points?
能说重点吗
I doubt
我怀疑
Supporters behind Zhou Zheyi
周哲一背后的支持者
It's night fog
是夜雾
I think you think too much
我觉得你想太多了
So do you have evidence?
那你有证据吗
Think about it
你想想啊
you go to thailand
你去泰国
Was he sent there temporarily?
是被他临时派过去的吧
Something happened as soon as you got there
你刚到那儿就出事了
This is definitely not a coincidence
这绝对不是巧合
You've been in contact with him for so long
你跟他接触这么长时间
Just no feeling at all
就一点感觉都没有
If you really doubt him
如果你实在是怀疑他
You can report him to the National Security Bureau
可以跟国安局举报他
no need to tell me
不用告诉我
You can doubt all this
你可以怀疑这一切
It's all my imagination
都是我的想象
But I still have to remind you
但我还是要来提醒你
Why
为什么
Because I can't forget
因为我忘不了
Your desperate look on the boat
你在船上那绝望的眼神
You told me when you were on the boat
你在船上的时候跟我说
if i were earlier
如果我早点
Just tell you
告诉你就好了
Your desperate eyes at that time
那个时候你绝望的眼神
i can never forget
我永远也忘不了
if i told you earlier
如果我早点告诉你
You can still be saved
你还有救
A visitor comes to visit
有客来访
Who is it?
谁呀
Zhou Diyi
周帝一
You go in first
你先进去
A visitor comes to visit
有客来访
Coming
来啦
Yao Yao
姚瑶
Mr. Zhou
周总
How did you come up?
您 您怎么上来了
I left my sunglasses in my car
墨镜落我车里了
I'll bring it to you
我给你送上来
Thanks for the trouble
谢谢了 麻烦
Well, I was just getting ready to take a shower.
那个我这刚准备洗澡呢
I won't invite you in
我就不请您进来了
I can't bother you anymore
是我不好 打扰你了
See you at the company tomorrow
明天公司见
See you tomorrow, Mr. Zhou
明天见啊 周总
Bye-Bye
拜拜
gone
走了
How does he know where you live?
他怎么知道你住哪儿
It's all in the employee information, right?
员工资料上都有吧
It's not good for him to see me
让他看见我不太好
Tangled up with ex-boyfriend
跟前男友纠缠不清
You're done
你都说完了
thanks for your reminder
谢谢你的提醒
come this far
走到这一步
It's my own choice
是我自己的选择
You should go back early
你早点回去吧
Yao Yao
姚瑶
I will think clearly
我会想清楚
what should i do next
我接下来应该怎么做
What I want to say is
我想说的是
Just in case he
这会儿他万一
I haven’t left yet downstairs.
在楼下没走呢
I'd better go down later.
我还是一会儿再下去吧
Be alert at all times
要时刻保持警惕性
Will use it tomorrow
明天要用的
Are you all ready?
都准备好了吗
Don't worry, sister
放心吧 姐
All ready
都准备好了
beef rice
牛肉饭
Come, I'll come
来 我来
Come on, give it to me
来来 给我给我
good
好
Thanks
谢谢
welcome
欢迎光临
Thank you, I'll pay you back
谢谢啊 还您一位
to myself
对 我自己
Tianyang
天阳
Come, come, come
来来来
uncle
舅舅
that's what you said
这就是你说的
That izakaya?
那个居酒屋啊
yes
对啊
You also know this place
你也知道这儿啊
something to eat
吃点什么
Pork chop rice bar
猪排饭吧
good
好
Okay, thank you
好 谢谢
Come on
来来
Let me introduce it to you
我给你介绍一下
This is ours
这位是我们所的
Heavyweight researchers
重量级的科研人员
A pork chop with rice
一个猪排饭
Dr. Bian
边博士
You sit, you sit, you sit
您坐 您坐 您坐
My nephew Gao Tianyang
我外甥 高天阳
Nice to meet you
幸会
Come and sit in Tianyang
来 天阳 坐坐坐
I didn't expect to meet you here.
没想到在这儿碰到你啊
Yes, what a coincidence
对呀 好巧啊
Why did you start eating again?
怎么又开始吃上了
This period is quite stressful.
这一段呢 压力比较大
It’s not easy for a long-time smoker to quit
老烟枪 想戒不容易
I've quit for a long time
我已经戒了很久了
OK
好不好
stronger than you
比你强
You didn't look at me two months ago
你没看我前两个月
Didn't smoke much?
都没怎么抽嘛
That's what I prove
那倒是 这个我证明
Me and your uncle Bian
我和你边叔叔
We both quit together
我们俩一起戒的
Mutual supervision
互相监督
Dr. Bian
边博士
you
你
You quit too
你也戒了
with your uncle
和你舅一起
Always eating sweets
老吃糖
I'm almost going to have diabetes.
都快吃成糖尿病了
You just love sweets
你这个人就爱吃甜的
do you know
知道吗
It has nothing to do with me
跟我可没关系
I'll try whatever it tastes
什么味 我也尝尝
You don't smoke
你又不抽烟
What can I eat to quit smoking? Really?
吃什么戒烟糖啊 真是
Boss lady
老板娘
Another sushi
再来一份寿司
Pack
打包
Lao Huang
老黄
Tianyang
天阳
Excuse me
不好意思
I am busy
有点事
I won’t accompany you anymore
就不陪你们了
I'll just take a few bites
我简单吃两口
well
好 好
If you have something to do, go on your own.
你有事你走你的啊
As long as Tianyang is with me, that's fine
有天阳陪我就可以了
good
好
You eat, you eat
你吃 你吃
Eat quickly, don't let it get cold
你快吃啊 别凉了
Etc., etc
等等 等等
Waiting for your meal to come
等你的饭来了
Let's eat together
咱俩一块儿吃
this
这
Thank you for coming. Please walk slowly.
谢谢光临 请慢走
Thanks
谢谢
your unit
你们单位
It's not even close to here
离这儿也不近哪
How can you
你怎么能
Find this place
找到这个地方来呢
I used to work around here
我之前在这儿附近办事
Have eaten here several times
在这儿吃过几回
Around here
这附近呢
Just this store
也就这家店
The taste is okay
味道还行
Especially this boss lady
尤其是这个老板娘
that's really
那真的是
People who cook food seriously
认真做食物的人
Are you familiar with her?
你跟她很熟吗
The boss lady is very interesting
老板娘很有趣的
Kind and sensible
善良 懂事
don't you feel it
你没感觉吗
I really didn't notice
我真没注意到
I'll pay attention next time
我下次来注意一下
How many times have you been here before?
那你前几次来
They all came here blindfolded.
都是蒙着眼睛来的呀
I am attracted to this kind of gentle and virtuous mother type
我对这种温良贤母型的
She is not my type
她不是我的菜
So what type is your cup of tea?
那什么型是你的菜啊
Dominatrix type
母夜叉型啊
no
不是
I find
我发现
Why do you still talk about women?
你怎么一聊女人你还
let me tell you
我跟你说
Don't underestimate the boss lady
你可千万别小看老板娘
From my experience of getting to know people
以我识人的经验来看
This girl is not simple
这姑娘啊 可不简单
Don't look at her
你别看她
Gentle and virtuous on the surface
表面上温柔贤惠
actually
实际上
She's not that kind of person at all
她根本就不是这种人
You can see this
这都能看出来
of course
那当然了
Just your personality
就你这性格
future
未来
Who can hold who?
谁拿捏住谁
I don’t know yet
那还不知道呢
What do we have?
我们俩有什么
It's manageable
可拿捏的呀
What if
万一呢
What happens after that
那以后的事
Who can say for sure?
谁能说得准哪
Okay, okay
行了 行了
uncle
舅舅
Stop talking about my boss's wife.
你别聊人家老板娘了
Even you
就连你
Sometimes I can't see clearly
我有时候我都看不清楚
Isn't that normal?
那不是很正常吗
They are all thousand-year-old foxes
都是千年狐狸
I eat salt
我吃的盐
It’s more food than you eat
比你吃的饭还多呢
Want to see something clearly
要想看清楚些什么
You still have to practice and practice again
你还得再修炼修炼
Accepted
服啦
correct
对了
How are Zicheng and Yao Yao doing?
子诚和姚瑶怎么样了
Really divided
真分了
They both seem to be
他们俩好像是
What do you mean it seems to be?
什么叫好像是啊
Come
来
Pork Chop Rice
猪扒饭
thank you
谢谢啊
I really think
我真觉得
You two are a good match
你们俩挺合适的
Eat yours
吃你的吧
Stop minding your own business.
你别管闲事了你
Boss, I'm going to stock up.
老板 我去进货了
good
好
I'll give you a piece
我捎你一段
No need for me to wander around
不用 我溜达溜达
Just around the corner and there you are
转个弯就到了
Then I'm leaving
那我走了啊
What's that?
那行 那个什么
It's rare for you to have leisure time
你难得清闲
next time
下次
Ask Zicheng to come over with you
约着子诚一块儿过来
OK
行
good
好
Drive slowly
慢点开车啊
Bye-Bye
拜拜
Your bugs have arrived
你的虫到货了
Okay, go there right away
好 马上过去
We have a situation we want to know about
我们有个情况想要了解
need your cooperation
需要你的配合
good
好
we want to know
我们想了解一下
Zheyue's situation
哲阅的情况
I have resigned from Zheyue
我已经从哲阅离职了
I don't know what else I can help you with.
不知道还能帮你们什么
Shi Qi
诗琪
if we didn't
如果我们没有
Find out your details
摸清你的底细
I won't come to you rashly
是不会贸然来找你的
What do you want to ask
你想问什么
About Zheyue
关于哲阅
Leakage of user information
泄漏用户信息的事情
I'm not sure about this
这个我不太清楚
Then let's talk
那我们就聊一聊
Agent mission game
特工任务这款游戏吧
How you look in the game
你在游戏当中的样子
Not as innocent as now
可没有现在这么无辜
crow
乌鸦
Am I breaking the law by playing games?
我玩游戏犯法吗
It depends on how you play
那要看你玩的
what game is it
是什么游戏
Selling information online
在网上贩卖情报
Do you think the network
你以为网络
It's a place outside the law
就是法外之地了
I just rely on my own ability
我就是靠我自己的能力
Digging up some dirt in the industry
挖一些行业内的黑料
What does this have to do with national security?
这跟国安有什么关系呀
Because of these dirty things
因为这些黑料
Matters of national security
事关国家安全
This is not just
这已经不仅仅是
An ordinary crime
普通的犯罪了
you have been
你已经被
Overseas espionage organizations are targeting
海外的间谍组织盯上了
very likely to become
很有可能会成为
their victims
他们的牺牲品
This has something to do with a spy organization
这跟间谍组织
What does it matter?
有什么关系啊
That's up to you
那就要看你了
What's in your hands
你手里到底
what did you take
拿了什么东西
It's a video I recorded
是我录的一段视频
What video
什么视频
Server room in Zheyue
在哲阅的服务器机房
There is a server
有一台服务器
always locked
一直被锁着
I feel strange
我觉得很奇怪
Since I joined the company
从我入职开始
It's always been locked here
这儿就一直被锁着
I'm from the technical department
我从技术部的人
Find out there
那儿打听到
Said the machine inside was broken
说里边机器坏了
No more use
闲置不用了
I'm very strange
我就很奇怪
In this case
既然这样的话
Why does it have to be locked?
为什么一定要锁上呢
I'm a little curious
我有点好奇
I just want to see
我就想看看
What's inside
里边到底是什么
Then I went to see
然后我去看了
Server is obvious
服务器明显
Everything is running normally
都在正常运行
Not broken at all
根本没坏掉
I find
我发现
Line information has been diverted
线路的信息被分流了
one of the information
其中一个信息的
Transfer object
传送对象
In Zheyue’s service records
在哲阅的服务记录中
Can't find it at all
根本找不到
I doubt it
我就怀疑
someone is stealing
有人正在窃取
server data
服务器的数据
or
或者
Zheyue has always been
哲阅一直以来
They are all working with third parties
都在跟第三方
Shared server information
共享服务器的信息
video material
视频资料
I have them all stored on the USB drive
我都存在优盘里了
Where is the USB flash drive?
优盘在哪儿
at my house
在我家
Set off
出发
Go to their house and get the USB flash drive
去她们家拿优盘
well
好 好
Tianyang
天阳
how's it going
怎么样了
Found someone
找到人了
On the way back to pick up things
在回去取东西路上
Where are you?
你那边呢
Never came out
一直没有出来
Boss, I'm going to stock up.
老板 我去进货了
good
好
This boss Zhang
这个张老板
How did you discover us?
是怎么发现我们的呢
I doubt her side
我怀疑她身边
There are other eyeliners
还有其他眼线
Secret whistle
暗哨
You are not alone
你身边不止
Xiao Yi should be alone
肖逸一个人吧
certainly
当然
Liu, where are you?
大刘 你们在哪儿呢
Shi Qijia
诗琪家
Wu Xigang left
吴熙刚走
I followed Shiqi upstairs to collect the physical evidence.
跟着诗琪上楼取物证了
send me the address
把地址发给我
Go check the community surveillance
你去检查一下小区监控
Maybe Ye Wu has already taken action
可能夜雾已经行动了
besides
还有
send someone
派一个人
Go support Wu Xi
去支援吴熙
receive
收到
Where’s the USB drive?
优盘呢
What's wrong
怎么了
I obviously put it here
我明明放这儿了
There is a backup in the computer
电脑里还有备份
Why is there nothing?
怎么什么都没了
Do you have any other backups?
你还有没有其他备份啊
have
有
Shi Qi
诗琪
What's wrong Shiqi?
怎么了 诗琪
go to hospital
去医院
what's wrong with you
你怎么回事
good
好
Liu called an ambulance
大刘 叫救护车
Send Shiqi to the hospital
送诗琪去医院
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
没事 没事 没事
You lie down for a while
你趴一会儿
Shi Qi
诗琪
Cuff him
给他铐起来
Don't move
不许动
Are you OK
你没事吧
fine
没事
Walk
走
Why did Shiqi faint suddenly?
诗琪怎么突然晕倒了
I followed her all the way
这一路我都跟着她
Logically speaking
按道理来说
No one should have a chance to make a move
应该没有人有机会下手
That unless
那除非
Don't touch it for now
你暂时不要碰
anything in the house
屋里边任何东西
Wait for the trace inspection team to come over
等痕检组过来
more carefully
再仔细地
Check the room
把房间检查一遍
Most likely the same as last time
很有可能跟上次
It's like Shi Lei was poisoned
石磊中毒一样
nerve gas
神经毒气
You are like this
你们这样
You and Da Liu
你跟大刘
Go up first and wait for the trace inspection team
先去上去等痕检组
I'll check the target
我去审一下目标
So clear
好 明白
Hi-tech
高科
I'll talk to him alone
我单独跟他聊聊
good
好
Why is it you?
怎么是你啊
Who are you?
你到底什么人
I am a Jiahui person
我是嘉惠的人
You are from Yewu
你是夜雾的人
let me go
放我走
What should I do if I let you go?
放你走我怎么办
I know your identity
我知道你身份
Find a way to let me go
你想办法放我走
impossible
不可能
Now it’s all people from the National Security Bureau outside.
现在外边全是国安的人
I'll be finished if I let you go
我放你走我就完了
Aren't you afraid that I will tell you?
你不怕我把你说出来吗
I know your identity
我知道你们的身份
You tell me
你把我说出来
Do you think you'll be fine?
你觉得你会好过吗
When the time comes, you and I will benefit
到时候你 我 嘉惠
Totally screwed
全完蛋
You are a Jiahui person
你是嘉惠的人
You don’t want to hurt her, right?
你不想害她吧
You heard me clearly
你给我听清楚了
The only thing that can be done now
现在唯一能做的
Just bring the news to her
就是把消息带给她
You came here for Shiqi, right?
你是奔着诗琪来的吧
Have you found anything?
东西找到了吗
has been destroyed
已经销毁了
Why did Jiahui want to get rid of her?
嘉惠为什么要除掉她
I have no idea
我不知道
Who asked her to do this?
谁让她这么做的
why are you asking me this
你为什么要问我这个
i have to know
我必须要知道
The secret in Shi Qi’s hands
诗琪手上的秘密
How important is it?
到底有多重要
Who will be threatened?
会威胁到谁
I only know the future
我才知道今后
How can I help you?
怎么去帮你们
time is limited
时间不多了
Are you trying to trick me?
你是在套我话吗
I only know what's going on
我只有知道什么情况
It won't be like this now
才不会像现在这样
caught off guard
措手不及
why did you appear suddenly
你为什么会突然出现
I am not responsible for this action
这次行动不是我负责
I just received a notification
我刚接到通知
I did not expect
我没想到
It was you who came here to see
过来看到的是你
If AirPlus
如果嘉惠
Tell me the situation earlier
早点把情况告诉我
Nor will you
你也不至于
Falling into this situation
落到现在这种境地
Why do I think you are lying to me?
我怎么觉得你在骗我呢
What is your identity?
你到底什么身份
Don’t you know my identity?
我的身份你不知道吗
I'm a little unsure now
我现在有点不确定
he has admitted
他已经承认
Attacked Shiqi
对诗琪下手了
Take it back for interrogation
带回去 接着审
good
好
besides
还有
Let the technical department check it out
让技术科查一查
his mobile phone
他的手机
Who have you contacted?
跟谁联系过
Understand
明白 好
Wu Xi, are you done?
吴熙 你完事了吗
I have left
我已经离开了